Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Chicks with Dicks
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Chicks with dicks
1994-1996
Bailey 18
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
13 v.; 18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Individual titles (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
All individual titles paperbound.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Chicks with Dicks
  - Transvestite stud, c1994; first printing 1985; CK_101_ (Box CK101)
  - She-male's torment, c1994; first printing 1988; CK_102_ (Box CK102)
  - 10-inch she-male, c1994; first printing 1986; CK_103_ (Box CK103)
    Scope and Contents
    Stamp on bottom edge: SODI
  - Transvestite star, c1994; first printing 1986; CK_104_ (Box CK104)
    Stamp on top edge: MAP MAP MAP
  - Millie/Willie, c1995; CK_106_ (Box CK106)
  - Paul, c1995; CK_109_ (Box CK109)
    "Price label on front cover: 14 AEN $4.95+tx Small barcode label on front cover"
  - Serving sisters, c1995; first printing 1983; CK_110_ (Box CK110)
    Stamp on top edge: 19
  - Tom, c1995; CK_111_ (Box CK111)
    Price label on front cover: 14 09 $4.95+tx
  - Her huge meat, c1995; first printing 1986; CK_112_ (Box CK112)
  - Endowed dominatrix, c1996; CH_101_ (Box CH101)
  - The dangling package, c1996; CH_102_ (Box CH102)
  - Her big surprise, c1996; CH_103_ (Box CH103)
  - TV recruit, c1996; CH_104_ (Box CH104)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.